(Sheldon:)-Well, then, you have my permission.
-I didn't ask for your permission.
(Sheldon:)Too late. No backsies.
(Howard:)No, no, listen to me.
Sheldon misunderstood.
(Howard:)What I meant was,
if we worked together,
(Howard:)there'd be too much of me for you,
not the other way around.
(Sheldon:)Howard, if you're going to lie
to your wife,
(Sheldon:)don't start the sentence
with "Sheldon misunderstood?
(Sheldon:)-That's a dead giveaway.
-Well?
(Howard:)Okay, fine. I did say that,
and I think it's true.
(Howard:)I think if we worked together
and lived together,
(Howard:)we'd get sick of each other.
(Sheldon:)But to be fair, he only said the part
about him getting sick of you.
For the love of God, why?!
(Bernadette:)What exactly do you think
you'd get sick of?
(Raj:)His only options here are to fake
a heart attack or have a real one.
(Howard:)It's nothing in particular.
(Bernadette:)Is it my voice?
Am I too bossy?
(Howard:)My arm is feeling numb.
(Leonard:)Nailed it.